{"quiz": {"questions": [{"Hint": null, "question": "What were vampires shroud-wearing undead beings who often visited loved ones and caused mischief in the neighborhoods in European folklore?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "they inhabited when they were alive"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "they inhabited when they were alive"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 189, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Were vampires shroud-wearing undead beings who often visited loved ones and caused mischief in the neighborhoods they inhabited when they were alive in European folklore?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}], "type": "mcq", "id": 188, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Who were vampires shroud-wearing undead beings who often visited loved ones and caused mischief in the neighborhoods inhabited when they were alive in European folklore?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "they"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "they"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 187, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "What were vampires shroud-wearing undead beings who often visited loved ones and caused mischief in the neighborhoods inhabited when they were alive in European folklore?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "they"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "they"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 186, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Is a vampire a being from folklore who subsists on the blood or life essence of the living?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}], "type": "mcq", "id": 185, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "What is a vampire?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "a being from folklore who subsists on the blood or life essence of the living"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "a being from folklore who subsists on the blood or life essence of the living"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 184, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "What were vampires they inhabited when they were alive in European folklore?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "shroud-wearing undead beings who often visited loved ones and caused mischief in the neighborhoods"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "shroud-wearing undead beings who often visited loved ones and caused mischief in the neighborhoods"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 183, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "What were vampires shroud-wearing undead beings who often visited loved ones and caused mischief in the neighborhoods they inhabited when they were alive in?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "in European folklore"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "in European folklore"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 182, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Who were shroud-wearing undead beings who often visited loved ones and caused mischief in the neighborhoods they inhabited when they were alive in European folklore?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "vampires"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "vampires"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 181, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "What is a vampire a being from folklore who subsists on the blood or life essence of?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "of the living"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "of the living"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 180, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Who is a being from folklore who subsists on the blood or life essence of the living?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "a vampire"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "a vampire"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 179, "skippable": true}]}}